A New Family Gate
Now is the time for you to drink this tea!
A masterpiece of fairness and purity
The gate of the house
Through the camera.
That's right.
The presence of a great person.
Thank you very much.
I, um...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Creating an atmosphere, creating an atmosphere.
So it's all about the angle.
Yes, it's all about the angle.
It's all about mood, isn't it?
Yes.
Well, let's get started. I look forward to working with you.
Now, let me introduce the groom once again. This is Mr. Masamune Matsui Honki. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
This is Mr. Matsuidera. Pleased to meet you.
Please give my regards to you.
Today, it's your own store, Mr. Matsuidera.
I'm making tea, the tea that was just put in.
Yes, please confirm.
Yes.
Good night.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching today. Have a nice day!
Okay, I'm going to go to the show.
Thank you for watching.
I'm hungry.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, we have the video from the mouse key person. Thank you very much.
We will play Dinamicide 2 after this. Please wait in your seats.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
This is really my first time with Mr. Nagano.
Anyway, his presence didn't make me feel any discomfort.
Somehow, our concentration matched well, or something like that.
I had such a feeling.
It was a bit strange from the beginning.
But first of all
I myself have never heard of Mr. Nagano
I've seen him on TV and in other advertisements
and I knew of his plays as well.
I don't know what's going on...
In my opinion...
She has a little animal-like cuteness.
I wondered what it was about.
I couldn't help but think of Mr. Nagano as a squirrel.
And a white squirrel.
I wondered if there was such a thing as a white squirrel.
They exist in Hokkaido.
It's a white variant of albino.
It's a rare kind of squirrel with a light pigmentation.
It's a rare kind of squirrel.
What I'm trying to say is that they are rare.
What I'm trying to say is
It's kind of cute.
It's cute and easy to accept.
And then there's that kind of rarity.
There's something special about Ms. Nagano's unique way of shining.
And when I actually meet her...
I could see that, first of all...
Her skin is like an indescribable
It's like an indescribable porcelain.
I don't mean fine-grained.
I mean, it's like...
I was surprised to find out that it comes from this beauty
I was surprised to find out that
And it's really...
I'm very detailed, so I did a lot of research.
She's been working since she was a child actress.
You've been in the business for a long time, so you've been working since you were a child actor.
I'm sure you've already been able to tune yourself to the atmosphere
I'm sure you're already good at tuning yourself into the atmosphere.
That's why I was able to work with a new director.
New director
I can work with co-stars
Immediately
Like this concentration.
The time it takes to exterminate the play.
You are the type of actress
I could see that you are the type of actress
I could feel it instantly.
In a good way, I was able to incorporate my own tension
In a good way, I felt that I was able to incorporate my own tension into it naturally.
I didn't realize you were giving me that many compliments.
It's probably the most praise I've received in my life.
I'm so happy.
Really?
Thank you very much.
Hey, it looks like you're in Hokkaido, and I'd like to go see you sometime.
I've seen your commercials since I was little.
I got the impression that you're a cool guy with a soft but strong personality.
But when I met you, my impression was exactly the same.
But when the camera wasn't rolling, he talked to me in a friendly way.
I was a little nervous when I came to the set, but he instantly made me feel at home.
But he made me feel at home in an instant.I was able to blend in instantly.
It's strange, but she's actually the exact same age as my daughter in real life.
And we have the same birthday in the same month.
So there is a sense of closeness.
So we started in 2004, the year the family line started.
If you count that as the first year, it's been 20 years.
So we have been working together since she was 3 years old, so we have a sense of distance.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
I don't think I can play the role of a tea master as well as I should, but I've been working with Fukujuen since I was three years old.
But there is actually a tea master named Mr. Taniguchi at Fukujuen.
He is also one of the developers of the tea with this family crest.
He has visited us before.
He is one of the developers of this family crest tea, and he once visited us at the site.
He once visited me at the site and said, "I have been focusing on one thing for a long time, pursuing that world deeply and profoundly, and then expanding it again.
The way a person who is working in such a way looks...
The way he looks at something, the way he moves his hands, is sharp but relaxed.
A single glance, a single movement of the hand, is sharp yet relaxed.
I was searching for a piece of that impression, somehow remembering.
I was trying to find out what they looked like.
But I was also looking for the significance of these two people with the tea disease.
The significance of these two people with the tea ceremony syndrome is that they are a symbol of tradition and innovation.
Whenever there is a renewal of tradition and innovation, it is important to bring a breath of fresh air.
I would like to incorporate such a breath of fresh air into the traditional part of my work, and then change again.
I would like to symbolize that we are always reborn anew, and I would like to incorporate that fresh breath into the traditional part of my work, and then change again.
Although Ms. Nagano has been performing for a long time, she has a very long career.
You have a long artistic career, but you are still very talented.
But at the same time, she has the strength of being true inside.
I think it's a good fit for me.
Thank you very much.
It's a first for you. It's a role that's quite a challenge.
I guess it's a little bit strange that I was there all the time today, but I was very nervous.
I was very happy to play the role of a tea master of a long-loved family crest.
It really is like running water, like a clear stream.
The design is also innovative. There has never been a PET bottle like this before.
The first house was originally designed with today's image in mind.
I'm always very particular about the bottle itself.
What do you think of this one, Mei?
I saw it for the first time today. Chirico glass?
It's glass, with that kind of work.
I thought it looked like something that was crafted with that kind of workmanship, and I felt that you were very particular about it.
That's right.
It's true that the way the light reflects off the glass changes.
The way the light reflects off the glass changes the color of the liquid, so the beautiful green color really stands out.
For example, in Kyoto, it looks like a bamboo grove in Arashiyama.
Also, it looks like a Japanese garden with gravel on the ground.
There are pictures painted on the gravel, right?
There is a sense of calmness like those sand patterns, isn't there?
I think so.
When I talk about my inner life, I have to talk about my negative side, about my nature.
I honestly couldn't find an answer to this question.
I honestly couldn't find an answer to this question, but I was thinking about this when I was confronting Mr. Meiji today.
I have always thought that my weakness is that I always start from a negative point of view.
In short, for me, this hesitation and regret is the driving force to move on.
So it is a necessary nourishment.
That's why I try to look at it in a positive way.
Anyway, Meiji-san, it's not just about the beauty of your skin.
I wondered why Meiji-san's skin is not only beautiful but also sparkling, like it's fizzing.
When I talked to her a little bit, I found that she doesn't feel, think, or drag things out.
So you don't get angry or have negative feelings.
Yes, I don't really have negative feelings.
They don't seem to have negative feelings.
That seems to be the same with his parents.
I think that's a wonderful way to raise a child.
So you have such a positive aura.
You have such a positive aura, don't you?
So, in that sense, I also have a positive aura.
The texture that I have is the same.
I think it's great to raise them in such a way, but I also think it's great to have a positive aura.
I'd like to update my mindset a little bit.
I would like to update my mind.
Well, what do you want to update in your mind?
Yes, that's right. I would like to update my mind so that I can respond to everything flexibly, but not every day the same thing happens, so I would like to be positive about the good things and the bad things that happen every day.
You already are, but you want to be more flexible?
Yes, I want to be more flexible. I want to be more flexible.
I know this may seem like a cliché, but I really do think that I am happy to spend my days in the morning sun these days.
When I was younger, I was perhaps a little more responsive to the sunset, or perhaps I thought that the slightly tepid, twilight-colored, slightly sexy feeling of the sunset was wonderful, but now I think that it's my birthright.
Now, however, I am more attracted to the sunrise, which has an air of brightness.
So, that child, no matter what happens, is always reborn.
So, the child, no matter what happens to him or her, will be reborn anew, but that child's attitude toward the sun, or the way the sun's light should be, is something that is a little bit cool, but it's not so cool.
I think there is also the fact that I am getting older and getting up earlier, but at any rate, I have recently been thinking that the morning sun is such a refreshing thing.
I went to the gym on a beautiful day to work out, and when I went outside after working out hard, I thought, "Wow, that feels so refreshing.
Am I using it correctly?
No, it's right.
Am I doing it right?
I mean, you work out for yourself, and your cells actually feel a little revitalized, and the world and the air feel fresher than when you go outside.
You are right. Yes, that's what I mean.
Yes, I think that's right.
I probably don't walk or run as much as most people do.
So I go to the gym and work hard to get my body moving.
I push myself when I have to.
This is kind of off topic, but...
You're a good driver, right?
I'm a good driver.
I admire people who can drive well.
I'm a bit slow in that area.
I'm a bit of a blur.
That's why I think people who are good drivers
They really know how to switch from one thing to another.
They have good sensors.
That's great.Excellent.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That's it.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to be cool even though I don't do this again.
I want to devote myself to something, right?
I'm so busy that I can't keep up with everything.
And because of my personality, no matter what I do, I always come back to it.
So even if I draw a picture or write a letter, I can erase and redo it.
That's why I'm thinking of sculpture.
If you cut it down, you can't put it back, so it doesn't matter if it's wood or stone.
And with that much perseverance, I'm going to create my own form, even if I don't know what it is.
Surprisingly, there are people who started kintsugi after they passed the age of shopkeepers.
So, if you try something like sculpture, where there is no turning back, you will find that your spirit is a little more sharp and clear.
I think my spirit would be a little more focused.
I'd like to see that.
I don't know if this is something to start in the spring.
I don't know if it's something to start in the spring, but spring is the perfect time to start, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I want to start playing golf.
Oh, for what reason?
I learned a little golf when I was in junior high school.
But at the time, I didn't really understand the fun of golf.
I was more interested in getting myself moving.
But when I talked to many of my friends who took up golf after they grew up, they told me that they started to play golf after they grew up, and they were very happy.
I heard that it's really fun to play golf with good friends on a nice day.
I'd like to join them, so I'd like to start with a round of golf.
Well, it's one release, right?
Well, it's one release, and if you go golfing a lot, you can get up early, whether it's 4:00 or 5:00.
I know a lot of people who say they can get up early, even if it's 4:00 or 5:00 a.m.
It must be such an exhilarating feeling.
I'd like to try it.
It's definitely a connection.
So, have there been any changes, big or small, in your life recently?
Yes, there have been.
Well, well, not everything, but the long pandemic is sort of coming to an end.
It seems like the long pandemic is coming to an end.
Everyone is getting out of the house a little bit, but it's not like it's all over.
So, I, too...
I've spent a lot of time cooped up at home.
I've made some progress in maintaining the garden and cooking.
One thing that makes me happy is that
The third of my three children is surprisingly still small, only 12 years old.
He will turn 13 this March.
But he is on the verge of puberty, so there are some difficulties.
It's a little bit difficult, but at the same time, I can understand what they're saying.
But at the same time, I'm starting to understand what they're saying.
My eldest son is 25 years old, and he is a little older than me.
Whenever my oldest son makes a mistake or something...
In other words, if my eldest son had failed in something, he might not have been able to realize it if he had not failed.
Even if you don't know the words, "Failure is the source of success.
I'm glad that I've grown up a little in that way.
It makes my life brighter.
I think that's why he became interested in cooking.
I started to help her a lot with cooking.
I went to a friend's house.
I would go to a friend's house and cook things like fresh pasta or lemon butter sauce.
He made it from scratch.
Isn't that amazing?
Once he experienced that, he got really interested in it.
The level was so high from the very beginning.
I enjoy the feeling that my second son has become a part of my life.
That's wonderful.
For example, is there anything that you continue to do with pride, or is there something that you are keeping to yourself that you cannot compromise on?
But it is difficult for me to keep going because I have an irregular work schedule, and it is difficult to keep going if I am learning something.
It is physically difficult.
So, I think that work is the only thing that keeps me going.
I started this job when I was in the third grade of elementary school.
I started this job when I was in the third grade of elementary school, so I kind of progressed without understanding the meaning of the job at that elementary school age.
As I grew older, through junior high school and high school, and understood the meaning of work, I was able to move forward with a positive attitude while still loving it.
I would like to continue to work with a strong sense of commitment to my job.
That's great!
Anyway, I started calligraphy when I was a child, and I can say that I have a little bit of skill in it.
But it's hard to get into it.
When I get into something, I find myself doing this, that, and the other.
Let's see... that's right.
Sometimes it's silly, but...
Do you know the babibbeh language?
Yes! Yes, I know it!
Civité berbe?
Huh!
Civitebelb?
Amazing!
For example, if it's Naga No Mei, it's called Navagabano Bomebaibi.
If it's Motoki Masahiro, it's Mogotobuki Mabasawa Hibirobotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebotebote
yobo kabarabako bobobo ba ba ba bibib bebe bebe kobo tobobo ba baobo
nabam dabarebekabatobobobobobobo yububub
debeki tabala baibi bina baat bobo hibi bibi
obo mobote babe bil bunda bakebe
Do you understand? Don't you get it?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
That's why they call it seyseidoukiolakanarukesakku.
Oh!
Well, I guess I'll just spread this babibibe word around.
It's called sabambutbolibibibibibibibibebebebebebebobombu.
What's it called now?
Suntory Yemon sabambutbolibibibibibiebibeebemobombu.
It's a babibibe word.This is a babibbe word!
Oh, that's great!
But haven't you heard of it?
Well, I heard a story about a gal who had a little reenactment of the Babibibe language.
hobonbutoboboboboba kabanobotababatibitobobohabanabashibitebemibitabacabatabatabambudabake be
Doborobo
Mababai bibi bibi
Habayibi
obosibi mababayibi
I don't get it at all.
Please put subtitles properly!
That's great.
I'm going to practice until we meet again.
So you just need to put the vowel followed by the same sound, babibibibe.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Nabba, gabba, gabba.
No bo, oh!
Yes, na-ba-ga-ba-no-bo
Me-bee-bee-bee!
Eh, but it's great mental gymnastics!
Yes, it is.
Amazing! Let's practice!
Yes, so I'll spread the babibibe word!
Oh, I'm looking forward to it!
Um, it's really not that interesting.
There was a time when I was a property-hunting hobbyist.
Whenever my friends who knew about it wanted to move
I would always get in touch with them and ask them what their budget was.
What is your budget?
They would send me information about the area they wanted to move to, and I would search for them and send them to them.
I still play the role of looking for a place and sending it to them.
It's amazing.
It's like, "Wow, that's really something.
I'm coordinating and searching within the conditions that I'm told.
And then I think, "I wonder if that girl would like this kind of thing...
I like to think about that kind of thing.
Yes, I think, "This girl would probably like a room with precious white color.
But I also like to think about whether she would like a room with tatami mats.
So I'd like to promote that.
I'd like to expand it a little bit.
How much would this floor plan cost?
It depends on the location.
I thought it would be a good price.
Yes, it is.